Finding Aid for the Program for Art on Film Records, 1951-1999, undated IA20008
Institutional Records and Archives
- Records collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1951-1998; undated; (bulk 1984-1994); Series II.; 51.8 Linear Feet; (45 boxes, 3 framed posters, 2 flat files)
  - Information on American film production and distribution companies and organizations, 1971-1998; Series II.A.; 10 Linear Feet; (23 boxes)
    - Fog Fine Arts Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Forma Art Assoc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Fox-Lorber, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Frameline, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Fusion Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - G Production, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - J. Paul Getty Trust Publications, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Goettler Associates, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-22)
    - Gospel Films, Inc., 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - GPN, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - GPO Film Unit, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Grapevine Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - William Greaves Prod., Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Green Acre Video, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Greenleaf Video, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Green Mountain Post Films, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Guidance Assoc., 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Grove Press Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Handel Film Corp., 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Hartley Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Alfred Higgins Productions, Inc., 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Highsmith, Inc., 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Holland Films, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Hollywood Studios, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Home Vision, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Home Vision, 1986-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Thomas Howe Associates, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Hudson Filmworks, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Icarus, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - ICA Video, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Ifex Films, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Images/Art New York, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Images Film Archive, 1984-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Independent Television Corp., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Indiana State University Audio-Visual Center, 1984-1986; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Ingram, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Inner Tube Video, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Intermedia Arts Minnesota (formerly UC Video), 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Ishtar Films, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - James Agee Film Project, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - James Agee (Film Project), 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Janus Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Jewish Media Service, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Journal Films, Inc., 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Richard Kaplan Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Howard Karno Books, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Karol Media, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kartes Video Comm., 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kaw Valley Films and Video, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - King Screen Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - KVC Home Video, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kino International Corp., 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kit Parker Films, 1984; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - The Kitchen, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Walter J. Klein Company, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kodak Video Programs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Kultur, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - L and S Video, Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Landmark Films, Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Learning Corporation of America, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Leonardo Project (ERN), 1991; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Librarians' Video Service, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Library Videos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Light Impressions, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Light-Saraf Films, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Lives of Saints, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Low Priority, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
      [Miscellaneous materials.]
    - Lucerne Film and Video, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Lutheran Film Associates, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Lynx Images Releasing, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Made-to-Order, 1985-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Manhattan Media Enterprises, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-40)
    - Manhattan Media Enterprises, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Sue Marx Films, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Masters' Mark, Inc., 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Maysles Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - McGraw-Hill contemporary films catalog, circa 1970 (Box 2004.IA.14-42)
    - Media for the Arts, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Media Guild, 1985-1986; 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - The Media Project, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Media West, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - MGM/UA, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Microworld House, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Milestone Film and Video, 1992; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - A Million and One World-Wide Videos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Milwaukee Public Museum, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Miramar, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - [Miscellaneous film programs, press releases, clippings], 1984-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - MMA Video Titles Available Thru Bookshop, 1981 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Modern Sound Pictures Inc. [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Modern Talking Picture Service, 1986; 1988-1989,; 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Arthur Mokin Productions, Inc., 1985; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - MTI Teleprograms, Inc., 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - MTI Teleprograms, Inc., 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Museum at Large, Ltd., 1978; 1981,; 1984,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Museum of Broadcasting, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Museum of Modern Art 1934, 1986; 1990,; 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Mystic Fire Video, 1989; 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Mystic Seaport Museum, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Nassau Library System, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Audiovisual Center, 1982-1983; 1990-1991,; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Center for Jewish Film, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Film and Video Market, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1985; 1989-1991,; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Geographic Television, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Museum of African Art, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Trust Film Library, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Native American Public Broadcasting, 1993-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New Day Films, 1984; 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New Deal Films, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New Dimension Films, 1986-1990; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New Line Cinema, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New York Public Library, 1982-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New York University, 1977-1978; 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - New Yorker Films, 1992-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Norstar, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Northstar Productions, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - NVC Arts International, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - October Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-47)
    - Jack Ofield Prods., 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Oklahoma State Univ., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - One West Media, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Opera Presentations, Inc., 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Pacific Arts Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Pajon Arts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Paper Tiger TV, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Park Films Ltd., 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - PBS Video, 1985; 1987-1989,; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - PBS Video, 1981; 1987-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - PBS Video, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Penn. State University, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-47)
    - Pennebaker Associates, Inc., 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Perspective Films and Video, 1982 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Phoenix Films, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Picture Start, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Pictura Films Dis. Cat., 1973-1974 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Prestige, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Producer Services Group, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
    - Public Media Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Pyramid Film and Video, 1988-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Quest Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Questar Video, Inc., 1993; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - R.R. Bowker bibliographic master file checklist, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-42)
    - Rainbow Educational Video, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Reading and O'Reilly, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Random House Home Video, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Rhapsody Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Rhombus, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Rizzoli: A.C. Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - The Roland Collection, 1992; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Roxie Releasing, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Samaya Foundation, 1990; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - San Francisco Center for Visual Studies, 1989; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Sandpail Productions, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-40)
    - Shambhala Productions, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - LA Sept/Video, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Silver Burdett Ginn, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1985; 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - S-L Film Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Smithsonian Institution, Office of Museum Programs, 1992; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Starr, Cecile, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Sterling Educational Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Stutz Company, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - SUNY/The Arts on Television, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Sutherland Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-40)
    - Swedenborg Foundation, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Syracuse Alternative Media Network, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Taunton Press, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Chip Taylor Communications, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Tele Hachette, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Terra Nova Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Texture Films Collection, 1972-1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Third World Newsreel, 1994; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Time-Life Films catalog, 1973-1974 (Box 2004.IA.14-42)
    - Time-Life Video, 1982-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Time Warner, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Total Marketing Services, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Time Capsule Films, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Treccani Video Library, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Turner Home Entertainment, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Twyman Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - UC Video [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Umbrella Films, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Universal Education and Visual Arts, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of California Extension Media Center, 1991-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of California/Santa Barbara, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Illinois Film Center, 1989; 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Iowa, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Minnesota, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Univesity of Southern California, 1984-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Texas at Austin, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Washington Press, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - University of Wisconsin-Madison, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Varied Directions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Valencia Entertainment, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Vesper Video, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Videfilm Producers International, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Video-O-Go, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Video Arts International, 1990; 1991,; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - The Video Catalog, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Video Data Bank, 1980-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-25B)
    - Video Encyclopedia, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Video Library Network, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - White Horse Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-68)
    - WNET/Thirteen, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Wombat Productions, Inc., 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Women Make Movies, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Wood Knapp Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Works by Woman, 1981-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-1B)
    - The Works, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Worldwide Travel, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - WPA Film Library, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Yes! Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Young Filmakers/Video Arts, 1982 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Your Video World, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Zanzibar Productions, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-68)
    - Zeitgeist Films, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Zeitgeist Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Zenger Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Zipporah Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
  - Information on international film and distribution companies and organizations, 1972-1997; Series II.B.; 6 Linear Feet; (14 boxes)
    These records are listed alphabetically.
    Records consist of catalogs, brochures, inventories, press releases, clippings, photographs, printed materials, correspondence, and reports, collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1972-1997 and undated, that describe international companies and organizations that produce and distribute films on art. Much of the material is promotional in nature (catalogs, brochures, and press releases). The bulk of the records are printed materials; any correspondence found within the records contextualizes these records, and is often in response to a direct query by Program for Art on Film personnel. Some of the information was used to compile the Art on Screen ("Critical Inventory") database.
    - Agence du Court Métrage, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Arts Council of Great Britain, 1984-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Australian Independent Film, 1982; 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Australian Film Commission, 1992-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Australian Information Services, 1983-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Austria Filmmakers Cooperative, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Base Audiart, 1986; 1987,; 1990,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - BBC Enterprises, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - British Film Institute, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Canadian Centre for Films on Art, 1972 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Canadian Centre for Films on Art catalogue, March 1965 (Box 2004.IA.14-42)
    - Canadian Filmmakers' Dist. Atlantic, 1986-1987; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - CBC Enterprises/Les Enterprises Radio-Canada, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Centre Du Film Sur L'Art, 1985; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Centre Pompidou, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Centre National d'Art et de Culture Georges Pompidou, 1984-1995; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Centre National d'Art et de Culture Georges Pompidou, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Channel Four, 1986-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - China/Consulate General of/People's Republic of China, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Direction des Musées de France, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - FACSEA (French American Cultural Services and Educational Aid), 1985; 1993,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - FIAF Bibliography of National Filmographies, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Les Films Constance, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Les Films d'Ici, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Films du Crepuscule, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Foreninsfilmo [Foreningsfilmo], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - German Sources of info, 1986; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - International Film Bureau, 1985; 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - International Film Circuit, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - International Film Foundation, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - International Film Programs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - International Tele-Film, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Instituto Cultural Itaú film and video catalog, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Israel Videotheque for the Arts: Tel Aviv, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Italian Cultural Institute, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Italian info: Sources, 1986; 1990,; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - Italian film catlogs (various), circa 1980s; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Kunst Kanaal/Amsterdam, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - Louvre, 1992-1993; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Magic Bus (Italy), 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60B)
    - Monte Carlo, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Montreal Festival Films on Art, 1984; 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Montreal, 1989-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Montreal, 1995; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Montreal Press Kits, 1996; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Musée d'Art Modern Villeneue d'Ascq, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Musée d'Orsay, 1988; 1992,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Musées Royaux de Beaux-Arts de Belgique, 1976-1979 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Museum of Modern Art of Latin America, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Film Board of Canada, 1981-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - National Film Board of Canada, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - National Film Board of Canada, 1985-1988; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Netherlands Information Service, 1984; 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Norway Norwegian Information Service, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-55)
    - Prague International Film Festival, 1987-1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1B)
    - Switzerland, Embassy of, 1985; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - TV Ontario, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - UNESCO Films on Art, 1949 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - UNESCO Films on Art, 1950 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - UNESCO Films on Art, Panorama, 1953 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - UNESCO Ten Years of Films on Art (1952-1962), 1966 (Box 2004.IA.14-42)
    - UNESCO catalog of films, 1970 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - UNESCO Films, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - UniFrance Film, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - United Nations, 1988; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
    - Venezia Cineteca Catalogo per Autori, 1980 (Box 2004.IA.14-4A)
    - Miscellaneous international publications, 1988; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-41)
    - Miscellaneous international catalogs, brochures, and publications, circa 1991 to 1995; undated; (1 box) (Box 2004.IA.14-93)
  - Information on films, 1974-1996; Series II.C.; 3 Linear Feet; (5 boxes)
    Records consist of catalogs, brochures, inventories, press releases, clippings, photographs, printed materials, and correspondence collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1974-1996 and undated, that describe individual films (both feature and documentary) that take as subject artists or art. Much of the material is promotional in nature (catalogs, brochures, and press releases). The bulk of the records are printed materials; any correspondence found within the records contextualizes these records, and is often in response to a direct query by Program for Art on Film personnel. Some of the information was used to compile the Art on Screen ("Critical Inventory") database.
    For feature film reviews, see Series II.E. "Subject Files".
    - Adagio, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Abode of Illusion, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Affairs of Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Akira Kurosawa's Dreams, 1990; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Alive From Off Center, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - All the Vermeers in New York, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Amadeus, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - America and Lewis Hine, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - America by Design, 1987; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - America: The Artist's Eye, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - American Art '85: A View From The Whitney, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - American Masters Series, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - American Visions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - American Visions Series, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - America's Pop Collector, 1974-1975 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Americas (Series), 1993; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Ancient Lives, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - L'Ange Et Le Barbare, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Ansel Adams, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Arena Brains, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Arnold Bocklin (1827-1901), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Arena series, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
      ["Art Line International Art News."]
    - Art D'exposer, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Art in Moscow, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Artists: Childhood Stories, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Artist's Choice: Ellsworth Kelly, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Art of the Western World, 1987-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Art of Being Human, The Series, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Art Underfoot, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Artists of America, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Arts Alive, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Art or Forgery, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Atheneum: Analysis of Form, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Basquiat, 1996; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Bazille, 1992; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Bauhaus in America, circa 1985; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Bauhaus in America, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Behind the Scenes, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - La Belle Noiseuse, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Belly of an Architect, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Bonnard Et Le Cannet, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Borobudur, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Boneshop of the Heart, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Bridge of Fire, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Building Sights, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Camille Claudel, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Candle in the Wind, 1985; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Carrington, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Caravaggio (Derek Jarman), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Caspar David Friedrich, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Casting Small Figures in Bronze with Jack Witt, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Cave, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Challenge, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Charles Roussel (1861-1936), 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Charlotte, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Charlotte: Life or Theatre?, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Civilisation, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Comic Relief, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Corps Perdus, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - A Day in the Country, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Degenarate Art, 1993; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - De Kooning on De Kooning, 1982 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Diego Rivera: I Paint What I See, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Drawing the Line: Portrait of Keith Haring, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Edvard Munch by Peter Watkins, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Edward Scissorhands, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Edouard Manet: Painter of Modern Life, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Einstein on the Beach, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - "Enquête au Musée,", 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Erl King, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Exiles, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Fantasy of Florida, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Feast of the Gods, 1990; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - French Painters Series, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Frida, 1987-1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Garden of Fantasy, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Gaudi, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Genius, 1992-1993; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Glenalbyn Drive, 1993-1994; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Going Up, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Going Up, 1984; 1989,; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)